# **SAKI BRANSON**

# **Project Manager**

From system solutions to promoting Lizzo's newest album, I have produced various digital/creative projects throughout my 5 years of experience. I have strong technical knowledge of web production, am skilled in various PM methods and tools, and as of May 2020 am available to legally work with a green card work permit without company sponsorship.

#### CONTACT

(347) 963-2877 saki.branson@gmail.com sakibranson.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Web Production Project Manager**

Atlantic Records (Warner Music Group)

OCT 2018 - JUL 2019 // NEW YORK, USA

(Left position due to student visa expiring and was unable to renew to work permit despite the company sponsoring)

- Work with designers, digital marketers, and developers to create promotional digital content for all label artists
- Monitor progress of all digital projects via Jira and ensure content adheres to brand/legal guidelines
- Facilitate technical conversations such as hosting, API integrations, and A/B testings with development team and acquire any missing resources
- Collaborate with CRM and E-Commerce teams to improve fan interaction and merchandising sales
- Work directly with SVP to strategize best practices for the creative team and digital department
- Train junior designers and digital marketers

# **Creative Project Manager**

Worlder Inc.

JUN 2016 - SEP 2018 // NEW YORK, USA

- Liaison between client, internal team, and vendors; overseeing photography, video, web production, and event management projects
- Track progress, scope, and budget of projects and report to client accordingly
- Manage client site content via CMS (Wordpress)
- Supervise and analyze client social accounts
- Assist in web design, animation, and photography creative work

# **Bid Manager**

IBM Japan

APR 2013 - MAR 2015 // TOKYO, JAPAN

- Manage internal teams of engineers and account representatives, and form proposals for clients such as Mizuho Bank and Shiseido
- Compile research data, design pitch decks, and lead projects from conception to final transaction

#### **SKILLS & TOOLS**

- Digital Marketing
- · Agile PM Methods
- SEO
- · UX/UI
- HTML/CSS
- · Adobe Creative Suite
- Adobe Analytics
- · CMS
- G Suite
- Google Analytics
- Microsoft Office
- Jira
- Trello
- Airtable
- Figma

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English Native
- · Japanese Native

### **EDUCATION**

#### **The New School**

MA in Media Studies

JAN 2016 - MAY 2018 NEW YORK, USA

Focus: Media Design and

Marketing

## **Waseda University**

BA in International Liberal Studies

APR 2009 - MAR 2013 TOKYO. JAPAN

Focus: Media History